http://www.bloomsteins.co.uk/privacy-policy/

Privacy PolicyPersonal informationThe use of the term personal information in this privacy statement means any information from which your identity is apparent or can be reasonably ascertained.Bloomsteins of Brighton collects personal information directly from you in order to conduct business; for example if you submitted an enquiry via our contact form, we may contact you using the email address you supplied.You can ask us to correct any errors or make amendments to personal information we have about you by contacting us, subject to you providing evidence of identity.We do not collect personal information about you if you are only browsing this website.Use of this websiteWe measure traffic to this website and use cookies through Google’s Analytics display advertising features to monitor visits. Cookies identify and recognise the computer, but not the person using the computer, when you visit our website.The use of cookies is an industry standard and most major websites use them. The data obtained is used to help us improve the website and each user’s experience. We may also use this information to offer you tailored content such as ads.If you prefer not to have cookies monitor your website usage, you can change the privacy setting of your browser to disable cookies or to warn you when cookies are being used. Google Analytics offers opt-out tools for the web or you can refer to your Internet browser’s ‘help’ information about how to change your cookie preference.The information we can log when you access this website includes:your IP or server’s address
the date and time of your visit to the website
the pages accessed
your operating system (for example, Windows 8 or iOS 8.1)
your web browser version and type (for example, Internet Explorer 11 or Chrome 37)
the time taken to transmit information to you
the previous Internet address from which you came directly to this website.
No attempt will be made to identify users or their browsing activities except in the unlikely event of an investigation, where inspection of the Internet web server logs is required by law (for example, by a law enforcement agency).For enquiries about privacy related to Bloomsteins of Brighton, please contact us.We use cookies to help improve your experience of this website. By using this website, you agree to accept cookies from this site. Accept and closeContact usFirst Name*Last Name*Phone Number*Email*MessageBloomsteins respects your privacy and doesn't tolerate spam and will never share your information (name, email address, phone number) to any third party.Privacy Policy Accept*By contacting us you agree to our privacy policyPhoneThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.This iframe contains the logic required to handle Ajax powered Gravity Forms.
